Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Staff meeting minutes, 1927-1938, 1951-1952 and undated RL.00749
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Use Copies, 1927-1938, 1951-1952 and undated; 1
  - Minutes of Representatives' Meetings, 1927-1932; 1
    - 1929 June 4 (Box 2)
      Industrial Alcohol; Foremost Dairy; Old Witch Ammonia; Pennsylvania Railroad; Irving Trust; Fleischmann; Goodrich; Real Silk Hosiery Mills; newspaper advertising; outdoor advertising; Clyde Thompson
    - 1929 June 11 (Box 2)
      Pennsylvania Railroad advertising; Stewart Mims
    - 1929 June 18 (Box 2)
      Foremost Dairy Company; outdoor advertising
    - 1929 June 25 (Box 2)
      Industrial motion pictures; recipes as promotions
    - 1929 July 2 (Box 2)
      Pennsylvania Railroad
    - 1929 July 9 (Box 2)
      Stanford University; Shell Oil Company; Laminex Door Company; Matson Navigation Company; San Francisco Office; Sun Maid; California Fruit Growers Exchange; Paul Cherington
    - 1929 July 16 (Box 2)
      General outdoor advertising Company
    - 1929 July 23 (Box 2)
      Pyrex Ovenware; Mellville Shoes; William Palmer
    - 1929 July 30 (Box 2)
      General outdoor advertising Company; outdoor advertising; Gilbert Kinney (appears to be a duplicate of minutes from July 16)
    - 1929 Aug. 6 (Box 2)
      McCall Agency; General Motors; Goodrich Tires; Goodyear Tires; National Broadcasting Company; Cream of Wheat; Pond's; Fleischmann; Pond's; radio advertising; Silver Fleet; Sears; South American advertising industry
    - 1929 Aug. 20 (Box 2)
      New business; News Bulletin; Glass Container Association; Texas Oil; Tareyton; General Motors; Sloan's liniment; tobacco advertising; South America; anti-American sentiments and propaganda [no minutes recorded Aug. 13 or 27]
    - 1929 Sept. 10 (Box 2)
      International Advertising Congress; South American Office; Goodrich; Germany; Australia Office; Stewart Mims
    - 1929 Sept. 24 (Box 2)
      Radio; outdoor advertising
    - 1929 Oct. 2 (Box 2)
      S. W. Straus & Company; magazine advertising; newspaper advertising; testimonials; copy formula
    - 1929 Oct. 8 (Box 2)
      International Department; Foreign Offices; Goodrich Silver Fleet; Market Conditions; William Palmer
    - 1929 Oct. 15 (Box 2)
      Radio advertising; Press Bureau's publicity activities; Chicago Office; San Francisco Office; International Telephone and Telegraph; Kraft; Libby; Crosley; Cisco; Shell Company; Publicity Department; John U. Reber
    - 1929 Oct. 22 (Box 2)
      General Motors Export; Crowell Publications; advertisers' productions; American Magazine; "talkie" films; John B. Watson; Stewart Mims
    - 1929 Oct. 29 (Box 2)
      Radio advertising; General Motors Conditions; Federal Reserve Bank; securities market; business conditions; Paul Cherington
    - 1929 Nov. 12 (Box 2)
      Research for Export Trade; industrial alcohol; Alcohol Institute campaign; Window Advertising Service; display advertising; export markets; international advertising; pricing; Henry Flower
    - 1929 Nov. 19 (Box 2)
      Chase & Sanborn's Coffee campaign; General Motors Export service stations; Overseas Motor Service Corporation; Maxwell House; Royal Baking Company; coffee industry; merchandising; automotive maintenance market; Lloyd Baillie
    - 1929 Nov. 25 (Box 2)
      New business; breakdown of Industrial Alcohol Institute appropriation; Curtiss Flying Service; Kodak; A&P; Eskimo Pie; R.J. Reynolds; Camel; Prophylactic Toothbrush; Shell Oil; outdoor advertising; John Reber
    - 1929 Dec. 3 (Box 2)
      Lux Flakes test campaign; newspaper advertising; testing advertisements; advertising art; Corning Glass Works; William Esty
    - 1929 Dec. 10 (Box 2)
      Meeting of businessmen with President Hoover; role of advertising; automobile industry; Packard; Gillette; American Woolen Mill; "dumping" of products; pricing; encyclopedia on advertising; international advertising
    - 1930 Jan. 14 (Box 2)
      Open discussion; how to run meetings; Radio Department; London Office
    - 1930 Feb. 3 (Box 2)
      Radio programs; B.F. Goodrich; Melville Shoes; radio station costs; newspaper rates
    - 1930 Feb. 13 (Box 2)
      Fleischmann campaign; foil yeast; nutritional yeast; testimonials
    - 1930 Feb. 26 (Box 2)
      Goodrich Sport Shoes; Beacon Falls; booklet "How to Talk in the Indian Sign Language" by Chief Buffalo Child Long Lance
    - 1930 Mar. 12 (Box 2)
      S. W. Straus & Company campaign results
    - 1930 Mar. 19 (Box 2)
      International Department; new international accounts; new international offices; "Dollarature"; "Europe as a Market" by Francis P. Miller and H. D. Hill; "Our Navy Under the London Treaty" by Lieutenant Melvin F. Talbot; Henry Flower; John Reber
    - 1930 Apr. 2 (Box 2)
      Textile industry advertising; Chatham Manufacturing blanket account; Lloyd Baillie
    - 1930 Apr. 9 (Box 2)
      Goodrich publicity; outdoor advertising; Maine Sardine Fisheries; Chase & Sanborn; industrial alcohol; Alcohol Institute; Clyde Thompson; William Palmer
    - 1930 Apr. 16 (Box 2)
      Report on radio; radio advertising; television; outdoor advertising; Cream of Wheat; Davey Tree Surgeon; Chicago Office
    - 1930 Apr. 23 (Box 2)
      Textile advertising; food advertising; Penick & Ford (Vermont Maple Syrup); Ovaltine
    - 1930 Apr. 30 (Box 3)
      International advertising; international markets; General Motors; Europe; centralized vs decentralized account management; Sharpe & Dohme Solution ST37 toothpaste
    - 1930 May 7 (Box 3)
      Eastman Kodak Company history; Kodak Park; Tennessee Eastman; Eastman Classroom Films; Lloyd Baillie; Walter Hine
    - 1930 May 14 (Box 3)
      Montreal Office review; Canadian market; French language market; general announcements; Woodbury Soap; Jergens; soap and cosmetics market; New Business Department; Robert Flood (JWT Montreal)
    - 1930 May 21 (Box 3)
      Scott Paper Company; nonfood grocery products; toilet tissue advertising; negative vs. positive advertising; newspaper advertising; retail floor diaplays
    - 1930 May 28 (Box 3)
      Simmons Company; Pennsylvania Railroad; magazine advertising; furniture and floor coverings market; advertising typography; magazine layout; Montreal Office; Raymond Browne
    - 1930 June 4 (Box 3)
      Importance of strategy in advertising copy; William Day
    - 1930 June 11 (Box 3)
      Analysis of business conditions; Arno Johnson; Gilbert Kinney
    - 1930 June 17 (Box 3)
      Review of new business; business conditions; sales analysis of JWT; Lloyd Baillie; Henry Flower
    - 1930 June 24 (Box 3)
      Los Angeles Office review; Southern California market conditions; Hollywood; film industry; Cliquot Club; National Electric Light Association; electrical industry; McGraw-Hill; TAT (Transcontinental Air Transport); Dan Danker; Stewart Mims
    - 1930 July 1 (Box 3)
      New business; Wall Street Office; L. C. Smith-Corona Typewriter account; office equipment market; portable typewriters; William Palmer
    - 1930 July 8 (Box 3)
      Radio plan work; Radio Department; radio advertising; advertising for Farm Board; grapes; Robert Colwell
    - 1930 July 15 (Box 3)
      Open discussion; Simmons account; Standard Brands; nutritional yeast; Royal Gelatin Desserts; Scott Paper; Pennsylvania Railroad; TAT (Transcontinental Air Transport); ST37 toothpaste; Pond's packaging
    - 1930 July 22 (Box 3)
      Publicity Department; Cream of Wheat; Scott Paper; Roxana Oil People; Carl Getz
    - 1930 July 29 (Box 3)
      J. W. Thompson Company in Spain; Spanish market and media; Portugal; Goodrich; Johnson Outboard Motor; Frigidaire; Arthur Hartzell
    - 1930 Aug. 5 (Box 3)
      Eastman Kodak; newspaper publicity; general business situation; new business; commodity prices; Carl Getz; Paul Cherington; Henry Flower; William Resor
    - 1930 Aug. 12 (Box 3)
      Showmanship in radio; George Faulkner
    - 1930 Aug. 19 (Box 3)
      The newspaper situation today; Media Department; newspaper advertising; rotogravure; Lux Toilet Soap; Dorothy Dix; Simmons; Edwin Cummings
    - 1930 Aug. 26 (Box 3)
      Foremost Dairies; Goodrich; Edward Fuller
    - 1930 Sept. 9 (Box 3)
      S. W. Straus & Company; securities and investment market; Kennon Jewett
    - 1930 Sept. 16 (Box 3)
      Counter and window displays; Gruen Watch in Europe; Standard Brands; consumer psychology; Benjamin H. Miller
    - 1930 Sept. 23 (Box 3)
      New business and general conditions; outdoor advertising; grape cooperative; cigarette advertising; women smokers; development of urban poster panel size; San Francisco Office; Clyde Thompson
    - 1930 Sept. 30 (Box 3)
      Advertising copy; radio advertising; Goodrich; Miller Tire; William Esty; William Palmer
    - 1930 Oct. 2 (Box 3)
      Special meeting; Printer's Ink; "Large Advertiser to Take Over Agency?"; General Motors; Campbell-Ewald; house agencies
    - 1930 Oct. 7 (Box 3)
      New business situation; chart of JWT business; Henry Flower
    - 1930 Oct. 14 (Box 3)
      Pattern campaign for international offices' smaller accounts; Brazil; Henry Miner
    - 1930 Oct. 21 (Box 3)
      Simmons advertising copy; "In What Position Do Healthy People Sleep?" by Johnson, Swan, Weigand; testimonial advertising; Aminta Casseres
    - 1930 Oct. 25 (Box 3)
      Magazine circulation; Atlantic Coast Fisheries; Canada; women's magazines; John Esty; Edward Fuller
    - 1930 Nov. 11 (Box 3)
      Vermont Maid Syrup; Nestle Milk Chocolate; Buenos Aires Office; Noel and Company; Penick & Ford Limited; comparison of newspaper circulation
    - 1930 Nov. 18 (Box 3)
      Trade papers; "A Great Scientist Looks to God" by George Gray; National Dairy Products; Kraft; Sidney Dean
    - 1930 Nov. 25 (Box 3)
      Scientific approach to advertising copy ideas; sales variation; Electric Boat Company; L. C. Smith typewriters; John Kimball
    - 1930 Dec. 2 (Box 3)
      Association advertising; Wood Office Furniture Association; color photography in advertising; hand-coloring photographs; Cast for Representatives Meeting Play; outline of a grocery store skit "August Schmaltz, Retail Grocer"
    - 1930 Dec. 9 (Box 3)
      J. Walter Thompson in Europe; John Watson
    - 1930 Dec. 16 (Box 3)
      J. Walter Thompson in France; "Plotting the French Market: Review of a Survey that Should Help in Selling to France" by Amos Stote; Karl Knipe (JWT France)
    - 1930 Dec. 23 (Box 3)
      Art in advertising; Elwood Whitney
    - 1931 Jan. 6 (Box 3)
      J. Walter Thompson Company plans for 1931
    - 1931 Jan. 13 (Box 3)
      Media aspects of radio advertising; network vs. spot broadcasting; broadcast coverage; Howard Meighan
    - 1931 Jan. 20 (Box 3)
      What the Information and Records Division of the Research Department is Doing to Help You; "reason why" advertising; legal aspects of advertising; F.A. Bell
    - 1931 Feb. 3 (Box 4)
      J. Walter Thompson's downtown (Wall Street) office; securities and investment market; "Investment Chalk Talk"; William Kennedy
    - 1931 Feb. 17 (Box 4)
      Advertising copy; "critical one percent" vs. mass audience; "Sales Training Course" by Standard Brands; William Day
    - 1931 Feb. 24 (Box 4)
      Johns-Manville Corporation; William Palmer
    - 1931 Mar. 3 (Box 4)
      Engraving and printing in advertising; color photography; four-color newspaper printing; Richard Huntington
    - 1931 Mar. 10 (Box 4)
      On the Practice of Selective Distribution by Richmond Watson; distribution costs
    - 1931 Mar. 17 (Box 4)
      British Columbia Packers Ltd.; Clover Leaf Salmon; Canadian advertising; Montreal Office; advertising recipe booklet; advertising test campaigns; Robert Flood
    - 1931 Mar. 24 (Box 4)
      Type in advertising; typography; BBDO; Standard Brands; international new business; Janet Cunningham
    - 1931 Mar. 31 (Box 4)
      Advertising appropriations; Stanley Resor; John Watson; Stewart MimsJ.M. Woodworth
    - 1931 Apr. 7 (Box 4)
      Johns-Manville advertising; Swift & Company; B. F. Goodrich; Silvertown Safety League; William Palmer; William Resor
    - 1931 Apr. 14 (Box 4)
      On the Handling of Radio Programs; Radio Department; radio production; Abbot K. Spencer
    - 1931 Apr. 21 (Box 4)
      Gorham Silver Hunt Club campaign; sterling silver industry; launch of new silverware pattern; jewelry stores; window and counter displays; Edward Fuller
    - 1931 Apr. 27 (Box 4)
      Lecture Delivered to Each Standard Brands Incorporated Sales Training Class by John B. Watson
    - 1931 Apr. 28 (Box 4)
      Hathaway Bakeries; market for bread; door-to-door sales; Lloyd Baillie
    - 1931 May 1 (Box 4)
      Lecture Delivered to Each Standard Brands Incorporated Sales Training Class by William L. Day
    - 1931 May 4 (Box 4)
      Speech made to the New Members' group meeting; Stanley Resor
    - 1931 May 5 (Box 4)
      Copy from an Art Director's Standpoint by James Yates; Standard Brands
    - 1931 May 11 (Box 4)
      Notes of the Speech Made by Mr. Richmond Watson to the New Members' Group Meeting
    - 1931 May 12 (Box 4)
      Methods of Determining Advertising Appropriations by Arno Johnson; charts on advertising budgets
    - 1931 May 19 (Box 4)
      Carter's Ink account; ink and fountain pen industries; Germany; long term advertising contracts; Clement Watson; Kennett Hinks
    - 1931 May 26 (Box 4)
      South Africa Office; history and description of South Africa; Francis McArdle
    - 1931 June 2 (Box 4)
      Copenhagen Office; Stockholm Office; Denmark market; Alpha Margarine; Alwether coats; Diamond Polish; Gluten Flour; A&P; "Chaining the Chain Stores"; "Uncle Sam's Peacetime Plan for War"; Philip Richardson
    - 1931 June 9 (Box 4)
      Cutex account; Wrigley; Kodak; Jergen's; William Resor
    - 1931 June 16 (Box 4)
      A Media Man's Viewpoint on Newspaper Copy by Edwin Cummings; Chase & Sanborn radio program; newspaper readership
    - 1931 June 23 (Box 4)
      The J. Walter Thompson Conception of Merchandising by Lloyd Baillie; General Foods; Population and Its Distribution; Swift Radio Program
    - 1931 June 30 (Box 4)
      The Production of Trade and Technical Advertising by C.F. Bell; magazine circulation
    - 1931 July 7 (Box 4)
      Johns-Manville; Pennsylvania Railroad account; National Outdoor Advertising Burear; outdoor advertising; Stewart Mims
    - 1931 July 14 (Box 4)
      J. Walter Thompson Company in Argentina; Plan and Data Form; C. Russell Pierce (JWT Buenos Aires)
    - 1931 July 21 (Box 4)
      Credit and business conditions; duplication of magazine circulation (two subscriptions in one home); John Esty
    - 1931 July 28 (Box 4)
      Scott Paper; J. Walter Thompson Company in Poland and Sweden; George Richardson
    - 1931 Aug. 4 (Box 4)
      The Federal Trade Commission and the Tainted Testimonial--Earle Clark; Royal Baking Powder; Standard Brands; Wrigley; FTC v. Raladam Company (U.S. Supreme Court)
    - 1931 Aug. 11 (Box 4)
      Problems of loose talk; production of radio programs;; prospects of television; Gordon Thompson; J.C. Penney
    - 1931 Aug. 18 (Box 4)
      Nestle's account' Lloyd Baillie; subway posters; concentration of effort
    - 1931 Aug. 25 (Box 5)
      News vs. Copy--Newspaper Practices (Savington Crampton); B.F. Goodrich; newspaper examples
    - 1931 Sept. 1 (Box 5)
      The Use of the Negative Copy Appeal--Henry Legler
    - 1931 Sept. 15 (Box 5)
      Plan Board activities (Ruth Waldo); Trade Department (Sidney Dean); Investigation Department (Richmond Watson); Radio Department (Abbott Spencer); Atlantic Coast Fisheries; Chase & Sanborn; Fleischmann's Yeast; Nestle; Kodak; Scott Paper; Smith Corona; Royal
    - 1931 Sept. 22 (Box 5)
      History of Kops Brothers account (William Palmer); general business climate; William Resor
    - 1931 Sept. 29 (Box 5)
      Harvard Bureau of Business Research Chain Grocery Store Study analysis (Richmond Watson); engravers and electrotypers costs
    - 1931 Oct. 6 (Box 5)
      Jergens Lotion account; Ruth Waldo; Staff Meetings speaker outline
    - 1931 Oct. 20 (Box 5)
      Radio Department; "The Vices of Free Competition" (Philip Cabot, from the Yale Review); John Reber; Amos 'n Andy; advertising rates; investigations; Richmond Watson
    - 1931 Oct. 27 (Box 5)
      Activities of the Antwerp Office (Adrian Head); overview of Europe; language diversity; Berlin Offce (Kennett Hinks)
    - 1931 Nov. 10 (Box 5)
      The United States Rubber Company investigation; Stewart Mims
    - 1931 Nov. 17 (Box 5)
      Magazine circulation; John Esty
    - 1931 Nov. 24 (Box 5)
      Rowntree marketing study; Arno Johnson; London Office
    - 1931 Dec. 1 (Box 5)
      Radio talent; Calvin Kuhl; Smith Corona
    - 1931 Dec. 8 (Box 5)
      Production costs; John Weber; electrotyping
    - 1931 Dec. 15 (Box 5)
      City Baking Company account; Lloyd Bailie; tests in radio media; John Reber; Jergens; name changing Investigations Department to Research Department; profile of Wrigley
    - 1931 Dec. 22 (Box 5)
      Report on chain drug store study; Federal Trade Commission; regulation of advertising; Northam Warren; fleischmann
    - 1931 Dec. 29 (Box 5)
      Wall Street (Downtown) Office; Melvin Woodworth; securities and finance advertising; economic conditions; Who's Who in Good Housekeeping Advertising Agency Records for 1931
    - 1932 Jan. 5 (Box 5)
      J. Walter Thompson Company in 1931 and 1932; William Resor; agency performance; Pennsylvania Railroad; Smith Corona; Johns-Manville; Sharp & Dohme; Research Department; outdoor advertising; radio advertising; new business; international advertising
    - 1932 Jan. 12 (Box 5)
      Discussion of copy tests; Lloyd Baillie
    - 1932 Jan. 19 (Box 5)
      The Modern Fetich--Organization; William Day
    - 1932 Jan. 26 (Box 5)
      Discussion of the independent grocer's problems; Kelsey Denton
    - 1932 Feb. 2 (Box 5)
      Competitive agency practice in radio advertising
    - 1932 Feb. 9 (Box 5)
      Standard Brands of Canada; Gillett; Magic Baking Powder; Fleischmann
    - 1932 Feb. 16 (Box 5)
      Pricing Policy in the Current phase of business--Gilbert Kinney; price vs. volume; Scott Tissue; A&P; China
    - 1932 Mar. 5 (Box 5)
      Responsibilities of the creative team; William Day; Advisory Committee; Creative Organization
    - 1932 Mar. 12 (Box 5)
      Study of comics; Ruth Waldo; comic strips and cartoons; General cigar
    - 1932 Mar. 19 (Box 5)
      The Cutex account (Margaret King); Ruth Waldo; B.F. Goodrich; Electrical Association; Actin
    - 1932 Mar. 26 (Box 5)
      General Cigar (Ruth Waldo); Pyrex; radio advertising (Robert Colwell); the Advertising Committee's work; William Day; Vermont Maid Syrup
    - 1932 Apr. 9 (Box 5)
      Headline writing in newspapers; Henry Legler; Vermont Maid Syrup
    - 1932 Apr. 16 (Box 6)
      Trade advertising; copy writers; Vermont Maid Syrup; Scott Tissue; Cutex Hand Cream; Ruth Waldo
    - 1932 Apr. 23 (Box 6)
      Chase & Sanborn's Coffee; Electrical Association; newspaper technique; copy tests; newspapers; Savington Crampton
    - 1932 May 4 (Box 6)
      Black Starr & Frost; Gorham; Fleischmann's; Portussin; Standard Brands dividend check folder; Vermont Maid; methods of producing copy; Ruth Waldo; N.W. Ayer; Young & Rubicam
    - 1932 May 18 (Box 6)
      Lux Toilet Soap; Rinso; Rowntree; London Office; British advertising
    - 1932 May 25 (Box 6)
      Lever Brothers; Lux Toilet Soap; Elizabeth Devree; testimonial advertising; comic strip advertising
    - Index of Topics, 1927-1932 (Box 6)
  - Minutes of Representatives' Meetings--Received from Chicago Office, 1927; 2
    - 1927 (Box 6)
      "Our Experiences in Newspaper Advertising"; chain stores; grocery stores
    - 1927 Jan. 11 (Box 6)
      "The Chain Stores and How to Deal with Them"; A. & P.; Lever Brothers; J. & J. Colman; Certo; Stewart Mims; John Esty; William Palmer
    - 1927 Jan. 25 (Box 6)
      "The Chain Stores and How Our Clients are Dealing with Them"; Hellman's; Krumm's Macaroni; City Baking Company; Baker's Coconut; Phenix Cheese; Welch; Royal; Lloyd Baillie; John Watson; Gilbert Kinney
    - 1927 May 19 (Box 6)
      Cheek-Neal Coffee Co.; Advertising Counsel
    - 1927 July 7 (Box 6)
      Distribution census; wholesale and retail trade; newspapers; William Resor; Paul Cherington
    - 1927 July 26 (Box 6)
      Real Silk; Piggly Wiggly; Scott Paper; J.C. Penney; National Radiator Company; Standard Oil; Meredith Publications; Dairy Farmer; Vogue; John Reber; William Day
    - 1927 Aug. 2 (Box 6)
      Welch Grape Juice; Welch-Ade; Gilbert Kinney
    - 1927 Aug. 30 (Box 6)
      Newspaper advertising
    - 1927 Sept. 8 (Box 6)
      Squibbs Perfume; Bovril; Ponds; Agfa; Nestles Hair Waving; Gillette; Campbell's Soup; Shredded Wheat; newspaper test campaign
    - 1927 Sept. 27 (Box 6)
      Nestle Hair Waving; United Fruit; American Radiator; Horton's Ice Cream; DuPont; American Bemberg Corporation; Crowell; Ladies' Home Journal; Scientific American; John Reber
    - 1927 Oct. 16 (Box 6)
      Piggly Wiggly
    - 1927 Oct. 25 (Box 6)
      Piggly Wiggly; Distribution Census; Sterling Remedies; Nestles Hair Waving; United Fruit; Union Tobacco; Log Cabin Syrup; Luden's Cough Drop; Welch Grape Juice; Simmons; Federal Radio
    - 1927 Dec. 20 (Box 6)
      European offices; Royal; Lux; Dominion Rubber Company; Gruen Guild; Continental Baking; Hooven & Allison Company; question of opening Toronto office
    - 1927 Dec. 27 (Box 6)
      A. & P. Tea Company; "Chain Stores in the Grocery Field"
    - 1927 Dec. 29 (Box 6)
      Globe-Wernicke; N. W. Ayer; General Motors; Ligget's Grand Central; Owl Drug Company; Piggly Wiggly; Norwich Pharmacal; Dow Drug Company; Plan Board
  - Creative Organization Staff Meetings, 1932-1934; 3
    Creative Organization Staff Meetings were held on a weekly basis between March 1932 and May 1933 with several additional meetings occurring in January and February 1934. Top company officials including the creative staff attended the meetings at which such topics as advertising practices, client campaigns, research efforts, international branch activities, and legal aspects of advertising were discussed. One staff member usually lectured on a specific subject. [Source: Accession record.]
    - 1932 June 1 (Box 6)
      Chase & Sanborn's Coffee; Drug Sundries; Royal Gelatin; Chevrolet; Frigidaire; Pine Tree Shilling; Knox Hat; sales conferences; promotional movies; Ruth Waldo
    - 1932 June 8 (Box 6)
      Carter's Underwear; French's Mustard; mail-order advertising testing; advertising copy testing; Pond's; Lux Toilet Soap; Chase and Sanborn; Fleischmann
    - 1932 June 15 (Box 6)
      Radio advertising; Hathaway's Bread; French's Mustard; Brer Rabbit; typography; Janet Cunningham
    - 1932 June 22 (Box 6)
      Chase & Sanborn's Tea; Pond's; Fleischmann's; Lux Flakes; radio advertising and drama; history of advertising since 1898
    - 1932 June 29 (Box 6)
      Gorham; French's Mustard; Viyella Fabrics and Yarns; health and vitamins in advertising; health products
    - 1932 Sept. 28 (Box 6)
      Scott Tissue Paper; medical opinions on abrasive impurities in toilet tissue; Henry Legler; European advertising; Henry Flower; Kennett Hinks
    - 1932 Oct. 3 (Box 6)
      Johns-Manville Company; William McKeehan
    - 1932 Oct. 11 (Box 6)
      General Motors Corporation; General Foods Corporation; advertising copy; advertising in the comics; Hawley Turner
    - 1932 Oct. 26 (Box 6)
      Jergens Lotion account; Ruth Waldo; Philip Richardson; advertising in Sweden
    - 1932 Nov. 2 (Box 6)
      Selling in relation to creative work in advertising; Lloyd Baillie
    - 1932 Nov. 9 (Box 6)
      Retail marketing; floor and window displays; Margaret Noon
    - 1932 Nov. 16 (Box 6)